borderlessaccess.com 2014-06-06

# Market Research | Online Panels | Survey Panels | Mobile | Business | Services

Borderless Access Panels has created this privacy policy to demonstrate its firm commitment to privacy. This policy describes the information gathering and information dissemination practices of the web site - [www.borderlessaccess.com](http://www.borderlessaccess.com/), as well as e-mail correspondence associated with this website.

This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected on [www.borderlessaccess.com](http://www.borderlessaccess.com/). Your visit to [www.borderlessaccess.com](http://www.borderlessaccess.com/)  is subject to this Privacy Policy. 

#### Personal information collection and use

We do not collect personally identifiable information about you, except when you provide it to us. For example, if you request for information, sign up for an email correspondence or ask about our published work on [www.borderlessaccess.com](http://www.borderlessaccess.com/), you may be asked to provide information such as your contact details (name, e-mail address, company, phone number etc.). When you submit your personally identifiable information through [www.borderlessaccess.com](http://www.borderlessaccess.com/), you are giving your consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. 

We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent, except as otherwise disclosed in this Privacy Policy. Except as otherwise disclosed in this Privacy Policy, we will use the information you provide us only for the purpose of responding to your inquiry or in connection with the service for which you provided such information. We may forward your contact information and inquiry to our affiliates and other units of Borderless Access Panels that can best address your inquiry or resolve your query. We may also use the information you provide in aggregate form for internal business purposes, such as generating statistics and developing marketing plans. If you do not want us to collect your personally identifiable information, refrain from providing us with any such information.

We may retain other companies and individuals to perform business functions on our behalf. Examples include, without limitation, customer support and fulfillment companies (e.g., companies that coordinate mailings). Such third parties may be provided with access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use such information for any other purpose. 

In addition, we may disclose any information, including personally identifiable information, we deem necessary, in our sole discretion, to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal proceeding or governmental request. 

#### Security

This site has the security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

#### Log files

[www.borderlessaccess.com](http://www.borderlessaccess.com/)  records details of individual accesses to its web pages. This information may include details of Internet IP addresses and browser types. We use this information to make your visit more meaningful and engaging. In addition, we use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site. Access by third parties to full log files may be allowed under controlled circumstances for auditing. Abstracted log information not showing individual's actual Internet addresses is provided to third parties. 

#### Notification of changes

We may revise this Privacy Policy. As we may make changes at any time without notifying you, we suggest that you periodically refer this Privacy Policy. Please note that our rights to use your personally identifiable information will be based on the privacy policy in effect at the time the information is used.
